{
    "id": "f7566b270fae47a19d46bda4f18f3f22",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I talked to that shy girl …………………… . she wouldn’t feel left out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "69c0a23777694d85899a5799a1c397cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is going …………………… .. get a new job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3897a61b56724153b22bcd80ad5ef7f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We stopped at the pub …………………. a drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7448b27cfd82434d83055a73077b4262"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is that cake …………………… eating?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ffab65e693f44438b8aade74cf44947b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Should I get anything ………………… . dinner?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7d29ce8e4de4a969f02eb46d9c16fc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shirt was too big for me, so I took it back to the shop ……………………… get a replacement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d4c01af3c854dcb82b8e72adb87da4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We started early …………………… . we wouldn’t be late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c1f9f13fbdc4e53a2c4e9d28ccc3caf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take some water ……………………… drink on the way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c2f0acc601c242f09085824f9150628c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You need a licence ……………………… drive a four wheeler.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f87dde48efd49228224637823f52698"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am leaving a bit early today ………………….. I won’t get stuck in the rush hour traffic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c071cce2ff924dbea58dd92f6ec2cc0c"
        }
    ]
}